bollyclips.com 2009-08-16

# Bollyclips.com - Privacy Policy

BollyClips.com values the privacy of information pertaining to its visitors. Information that may be collected when people visit this site Bollyclips.com may include the number of visits to the site, the average time spent on the site, the pages viewed by our visitors, the number queries per session and the specific text of the queries submitted. This information allows us to make modifications to the content and design of the web site to more effectively serve the interests of our visitors. We do not use or disclose information about your individual visits to our web site or information that you may give us, such as your name, email address, to any outside sources. We will not use information about you without your permission and will provide the means for you to manage and control the information that you have provided. We will enable you to communicate your privacy concerns to us and  we will respond to them appropriately. We do not disclose any personal information to advertisers and for other marketing and promotional purposes that could be used to personally identify you, such as your password. 

###   
Advertisers

Bollyclips.com allows other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within the Bollyclips.com site. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on the Sites. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies or JavaScript) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content you see. We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information.   
You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers or ad networks for more information on their practices and for instructions on how to opt-out of certain practices. Bollyclips's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.  

### Cookies

We do not store any personal information in cookies, nor do we use cookies to obtain any personal information from you. At this time, Cookies are not used on the Bollyclips.com site.   

### Notice Regarding Children 

If you are a child under age 13, please do not use this site. We at BollyClips.com take the online safety of children very seriously. Bollyclips.com website is directed to adults. we have no way of distinguishing the age of individuals who access our Website, and so we carry out the same Privacy Policy for individuals of all ages. If you are over the age of 13 but under the age of 18, review this Agreement and Privacy Policy with a parent or guardian. We do not allow children under the age of 13 to obtain Member IDs, and we do not intentionally collect any personal information from children under 13.  
If a child has provided us with personally-identifying information without parental or guardian consent, the parent or guardian should contact us to remove the information and opt out of promotional opportunities.  

### Registration Forms

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (eg. name and email).

Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site.   
We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. 

### Security

Your email address information is stored in a protected directory. Access is restricted to Bollyclips.com staff. No data transmission over the Internet or any network can be guaranteed to be perfectly secure. As a result, while we try to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. 

### Sharing Information

Bollyclips.com does not share, sell or rent your email addresses to outside third parties. Personally identifiable information will only be disclosed due to law or court demands (see our legal disclaimer below for more information)  

### External Links

This site contains links to other sites. Bollyclips.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. The Privacy Policy of an advertiser, promotional service, or third party link appearing at our site may differ from ours. We encourage you to read that policy before responding to the offer.

### Notification of Changes

Please note this Privacy Policy will change from time to time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of our site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. Information collected prior to the time any change is posted will be used according to the rules and laws that applied at the time the information was collected.

Legal Disclaimer Though we make every effort to preserve your privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with a legal process served on our Website.

### Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact [here](http://www.bollyclips.com/about/aboutus.php). 

### Disclaimer

Bollyclips.com does not store/host any files on its server. We only index and link to content provided by other sites. Bollyclips.com  is not necessarily affiliated with any of the vidoes displayed from YouTube.com, Google Video, GoFish.com, ApnaTube.com & Metacafe.com published on this  web site. While we strive to provide useful, quality videos, we make no claims or guarantees about the accuracy, completeness, or reliability of any information they contain. Videos are provided for entertainment purposes only and should not necessarily be taken as facts. Bollyclips.com does not accept any responsibility or liability for the use or misuse of information provided by any videos on this site. Bollyclips.com do not publish or host the videos that are linked or displayed to on Bollyclips.com and have no way of controlling the publishers or the servers on which the videos are hosted. Thus, if you want a piece of content removed from circulation, the best way to do that is to contact the website that hosts the video, not us.

**Date Last Modified:**  
This Privacy Notice was last modified October 2nd, 2008.
